{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815154916","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815154916"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" bbcf8599-0675-473c-8162-88aed48dfe73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" tamaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815160029","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815160029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" bbcf8599-0675-473c-8162-88aed48dfe73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" kofia"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815168263","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815168263"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" bbcf8599-0675-473c-8162-88aed48dfe73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" kukaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815174792","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815174792"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" bbcf8599-0675-473c-8162-88aed48dfe73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" alama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815186007","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815186007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" bbcf8599-0675-473c-8162-88aed48dfe73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" mungu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815191533","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815191533"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" bbcf8599-0675-473c-8162-88aed48dfe73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" miguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815202171","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815202170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" bbcf8599-0675-473c-8162-88aed48dfe73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815206465","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815206465"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" bbcf8599-0675-473c-8162-88aed48dfe73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815220296","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815220296"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 164c609a-6a63-4431-82c3-d4d44b9e53bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shina"," userResponse":" shina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815224356","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815224356"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 164c609a-6a63-4431-82c3-d4d44b9e53bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815272951","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815272950"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 164c609a-6a63-4431-82c3-d4d44b9e53bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815288067","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815288067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mvua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815293946","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815293946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mvua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" vu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815300836","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815300835"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mvua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" vu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815307664","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815307664"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mvua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" vu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815313573","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815313573"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mvua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 5"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815314650","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815314650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mvua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vu"," userResponse":" vu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815315711","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815315710"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mvua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815319714","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815319714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zabibu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" za"," userResponse":" za"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815320620","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815320620"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zabibu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bi"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815327273","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815327273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zabibu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" bi"," userResponse":" bi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815328239","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815328239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_zabibu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815333153","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815333152"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mjomba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815333645","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815333645"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mjomba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815339802","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815339802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mjomba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" jo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815340513","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815340513"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mjomba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815345389","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815345389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_watoto"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815345926","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815345925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_watoto"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" to"," userResponse":" to"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815346405","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815346405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_watoto"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" to"," userResponse":" to"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815351309","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815351309"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mahindi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815351801","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815351801"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mahindi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hi"," userResponse":" hi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815352502","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815352502"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mahindi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndi"," userResponse":" ndi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815356202","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815356202"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hasira"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815356932","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815356932"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hasira"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815357257","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815357257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_hasira"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815362610","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815362610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_treni"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815363852","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815363852"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_treni"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" re"," userResponse":" re"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815364656","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815364656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_treni"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815368707","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815368706"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_harusi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815369137","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815369137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_harusi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ru"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815375688","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815375688"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_harusi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ru"," userResponse":" ru"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815376372","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815376372"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_harusi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815382652","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815382652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_runinga"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ru"," userResponse":" ru"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815382983","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815382983"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_runinga"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" nga"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815389012","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815389012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_runinga"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815390030","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815390030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_runinga"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nga"," userResponse":" nga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815395274","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815395274"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sabuni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sa"," userResponse":" sa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815395615","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815395615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sabuni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815396025","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815396025"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sabuni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815398380","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815398380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_sabuni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815411908","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815411908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_sabuni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815423650","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815423650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_sabuni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815428700","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815428699"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 01cfd34a-a17b-4a6a-a908-665d80bfb210"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_sabuni"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815428771","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815428771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 69c13cc2-ef99-4f21-8cff-d135319a7312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" 0"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815434616","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815434616"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 69c13cc2-ef99-4f21-8cff-d135319a7312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 0"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815439696","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815439696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 69c13cc2-ef99-4f21-8cff-d135319a7312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 0"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815450337","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815450337"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkunga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUNGA"," userResponse":" MKUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815454753","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815454753"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkunga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUNGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815456317","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815456317"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zamani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815460359","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815460359"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zamani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815461940","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815461940"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andika"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815465478","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815465478"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" andika"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815467056","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815467056"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hasira"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" HASIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815470827","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815470827"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hasira"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815472395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815472395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dadako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADAKO"," userResponse":" DADAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815475996","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815475996"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dadako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815477560","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815477560"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tomaso"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOMASO"," userResponse":" TOMASO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815481395","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815481395"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tomaso"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOMASO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815482965","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815482965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mchovu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHOVU"," userResponse":" MCHOVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815486420","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815486420"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mchovu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHOVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815487978","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815487978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wadogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815492146","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815492146"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wadogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815493708","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815493707"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mizizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIZI"," userResponse":" MIZIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815497372","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815497372"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mizizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815498942","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815498942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hawezi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWEZI"," userResponse":" HAWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815502826","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815502826"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hawezi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWEZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815504834","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815504834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" hawezi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815505018","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815505018"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hawezi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWEZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815513080","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815513079"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" ca39072a-2e7f-4330-ab14-5b52e2b0e207"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" hawezi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815525066","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815525066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" d10216fc-8bbf-4377-94a2-46f79316ace8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815525650","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815525650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" d10216fc-8bbf-4377-94a2-46f79316ace8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815526304","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815526303"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" d10216fc-8bbf-4377-94a2-46f79316ace8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815526447","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815526447"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" d10216fc-8bbf-4377-94a2-46f79316ace8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815526821","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815526821"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" d10216fc-8bbf-4377-94a2-46f79316ace8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815527225","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815527225"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" d10216fc-8bbf-4377-94a2-46f79316ace8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815528328","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815528327"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" d10216fc-8bbf-4377-94a2-46f79316ace8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815529321","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815529321"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" d10216fc-8bbf-4377-94a2-46f79316ace8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TUKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815529885","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815529885"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" d10216fc-8bbf-4377-94a2-46f79316ace8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815530050","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815530050"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" d10216fc-8bbf-4377-94a2-46f79316ace8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815530864","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815530863"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" d10216fc-8bbf-4377-94a2-46f79316ace8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815533028","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815533027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" d10216fc-8bbf-4377-94a2-46f79316ace8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815535115","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815535115"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" d10216fc-8bbf-4377-94a2-46f79316ace8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815536528","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815536528"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" d10216fc-8bbf-4377-94a2-46f79316ace8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815549706","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815549705"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" d10216fc-8bbf-4377-94a2-46f79316ace8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815549821","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815549820"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" d10216fc-8bbf-4377-94a2-46f79316ace8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815549992","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815549991"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" d10216fc-8bbf-4377-94a2-46f79316ace8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815554628","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815554627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" d10216fc-8bbf-4377-94a2-46f79316ace8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815567685","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815567685"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 9edbbef8-1622-4602-b98f-6d7f8cd38f5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_harufu_chache-harufu-asijue"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" harufu"," userResponse":" harufu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815583275","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815583275"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 9edbbef8-1622-4602-b98f-6d7f8cd38f5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_baraka_baraka-ngamia-kupata"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" baraka"," userResponse":" baraka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815589600","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815589600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 9edbbef8-1622-4602-b98f-6d7f8cd38f5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jijini_jijini-sakima-sahani"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jijini"," userResponse":" jijini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815595316","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815595315"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 9edbbef8-1622-4602-b98f-6d7f8cd38f5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_maisha_maisha-nyimbo-mpishi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" maisha"," userResponse":" maisha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815606796","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815606796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 9edbbef8-1622-4602-b98f-6d7f8cd38f5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_naweza_zabibu-alitia-naweza"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" naweza"," userResponse":" naweza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815615358","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815615358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 9edbbef8-1622-4602-b98f-6d7f8cd38f5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mtende_nanuka-mtende-nataka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mtende"," userResponse":" mtende"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815623850","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815623850"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 9edbbef8-1622-4602-b98f-6d7f8cd38f5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuleta_dakika-kuleta-vidogo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuleta"," userResponse":" kuleta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815630461","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815630461"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 9edbbef8-1622-4602-b98f-6d7f8cd38f5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sokoni_huwezi-sokoni-ghafla"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sokoni"," userResponse":" sokoni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815636264","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815636264"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 9edbbef8-1622-4602-b98f-6d7f8cd38f5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nywele_maguru-kuhusu-nywele"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nywele"," userResponse":" nywele"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815642888","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815642888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 9edbbef8-1622-4602-b98f-6d7f8cd38f5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyumba_vijito-huruma-nyumba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyumba"," userResponse":" nyumba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815648615","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815648615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 9edbbef8-1622-4602-b98f-6d7f8cd38f5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_nyumba_vijito-huruma-nyumba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815654557","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815654556"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 9edbbef8-1622-4602-b98f-6d7f8cd38f5e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nyumba_vijito-huruma-nyumba"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815668654","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815668654"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kwa"," userResponse":" kwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815670047","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815670047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" he"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815677054","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815677054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" he"," userResponse":" he"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815678035","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815678035"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815682648","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815682648"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anguka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815684187","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815684187"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anguka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815685050","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815685050"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_anguka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815691758","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815691758"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wadudu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815693127","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815693127"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wadudu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" du"," userResponse":" du"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815694015","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815694015"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wadudu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" du"," userResponse":" du"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815699440","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815699439"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_redio"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" re"," userResponse":" re"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815700387","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815700387"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_redio"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" di"," userResponse":" di"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815701046","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815701046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_redio"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815705889","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815705889"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ingia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815707155","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815707155"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ingia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngi"," userResponse":" ngi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815707718","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815707718"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_ingia"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815714708","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815714708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_papai"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815715220","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815715219"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_papai"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815716126","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815716126"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_papai"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815719893","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815719892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_gauni"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815721422","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815721422"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_gauni"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815721874","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815721874"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_gauni"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815726170","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815726169"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sahani"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sa"," userResponse":" sa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815726587","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815726587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sahani"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815726896","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815726895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sahani"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815730747","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815730747"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_angani"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815731078","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815731078"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_angani"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nga"," userResponse":" nga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815731352","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815731351"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_angani"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815735870","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815735870"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sikio"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" si"," userResponse":" si"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815736339","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815736339"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sikio"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815742608","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815742608"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sikio"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815743335","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815743335"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sikio"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815745902","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815745901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_sikio"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815750597","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815750596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 43b9dc40-57ab-42c1-99c6-edc58969f5d9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_sikio"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815763158","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815763158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 37807cac-0051-428d-a686-edb0d2879516"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mashua_mzinga-mashua-mpunzi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mashua"," userResponse":" mashua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815770076","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815770075"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 37807cac-0051-428d-a686-edb0d2879516"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mashua_mzinga-mashua-mpunzi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815775450","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815775449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 37807cac-0051-428d-a686-edb0d2879516"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mashua_mzinga-mashua-mpunzi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815775574","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815775574"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" f609f3ff-436b-4639-a621-0dbdb37e3390"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" 0"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815795376","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815795376"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" f609f3ff-436b-4639-a621-0dbdb37e3390"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 0"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815800672","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815800672"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" f609f3ff-436b-4639-a621-0dbdb37e3390"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 0"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815807688","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815807688"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" f609f3ff-436b-4639-a621-0dbdb37e3390"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 0"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815813314","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815813314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" f609f3ff-436b-4639-a621-0dbdb37e3390"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 0"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815828232","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815828232"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpira"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815829173","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815829172"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpira"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815829678","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815829677"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mpira"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815834350","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815834350"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_haraka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815834871","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815834871"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_haraka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815835357","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815835357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_haraka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815839758","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815839758"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkono"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815840292","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815840291"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkono"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" no"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815846314","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815846314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkono"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815846964","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815846964"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mkono"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" no"," userResponse":" no"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815851635","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815851635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wadudu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wa"," userResponse":" wa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815852950","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815852950"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wadudu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" du"," userResponse":" du"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815853387","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815853387"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_wadudu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" du"," userResponse":" du"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815858392","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815858391"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_papai"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815860230","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815860230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_papai"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815860760","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815860760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_papai"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815866758","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815866757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mjomba"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815867039","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815867038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mjomba"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815873403","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815873403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mjomba"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" jo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815874010","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815874010"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mjomba"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815878973","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815878973"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_shangazi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sha"," userResponse":" sha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815880195","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815880195"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_shangazi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nga"," userResponse":" nga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815880699","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815880699"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_shangazi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" zi"," userResponse":" zi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815885755","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815885755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwa"," userResponse":" mwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815886396","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815886396"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815886635","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815886635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mu"," userResponse":" mu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815890924","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815890924"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nguruwe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815891391","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815891391"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nguruwe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ru"," userResponse":" ru"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815891784","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815891784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nguruwe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" we"," userResponse":" we"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815895477","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815895477"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_sahani"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sa"," userResponse":" sa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815895514","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815895514"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_sahani"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815902599","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815902598"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_sahani"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815939995","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815939994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 66ab284d-0efb-4f95-a385-2fba0ddf3b94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_sahani"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815947154","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815947154"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 47bfa0f5-3443-490e-82c1-a05f7eddf06b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815948498","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815948497"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 47bfa0f5-3443-490e-82c1-a05f7eddf06b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815948586","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815948586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" 47bfa0f5-3443-490e-82c1-a05f7eddf06b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815962227","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815962227"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kiatu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ki"," userResponse":" ki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815963810","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815963810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kiatu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815964168","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815964168"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kiatu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tu"," userResponse":" tu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815969173","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815969173"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jikoni"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815969642","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815969642"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jikoni"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815975904","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815975904"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jikoni"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815976520","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815976520"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_jikoni"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ni"," userResponse":" ni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815989337","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815989336"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_toroli"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" to"," userResponse":" to"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815990139","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815990139"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_toroli"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ro"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815991157","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815991157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_toroli"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815996239","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815996239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_endesha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815997008","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815997008"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_endesha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nde"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549815997316","data":{"timestamp":" 1549815997315"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_endesha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sha"," userResponse":" sha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816001208","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816001208"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vikapu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vi"," userResponse":" vi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816001576","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816001575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vikapu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ka"," userResponse":" ka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816002046","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816002046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_vikapu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816008052","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816008052"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mlango"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816008376","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816008376"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mlango"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" ngo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816014235","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816014235"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mlango"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" la"," userResponse":" la"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816014800","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816014800"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mlango"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngo"," userResponse":" ngo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816025177","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816025177"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_godoro"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816026946","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816026946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_godoro"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" do"," userResponse":" do"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816027801","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816027801"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_godoro"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ro"," userResponse":" ro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816033028","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816033028"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mlima"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816033857","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816033857"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mlima"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816034166","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816034166"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mlima"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816038419","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816038419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ma"," userResponse":" ma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816038725","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816038725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816039246","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816039246"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_maua"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816045930","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816045930"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_harufu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ha"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816046595","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816046594"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_harufu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ru"," userResponse":" fu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816052986","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816052985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_harufu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ru"," userResponse":" ru"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816053583","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816053583"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_harufu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fu"," userResponse":" fu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816055679","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816055675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_harufu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816060497","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816060496"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" e4c02de0-ef9c-44e8-87f3-1a318353a718"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_3__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_3"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_harufu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.len-6.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549816097857","data":{"timestamp":" 1549816097857"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_191210"," gameId":" af25975d-0d78-43a1-9c7c-33b88f3ae8d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.len-6.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kuleta"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}